<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fumiya Matsuzaki</title><link>https://trigger-fk.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Fumiya Matsuzaki</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://trigger-fk.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://trigger-fk.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://trigger-fk.github.io/about/</guid><description>I am a Ph.D. student at Kyushu University, Joint Graduate School of Mathematics for Innovation. Currently, I work at the Control &amp;amp; Optimization Laboratory, advised by Associate Professor Kaoru Yamamoto.
My research interests lie in control theory, especially in applying control-theoretic methods to real-world systems such as robots and quadcopters. In particular, I aim to evaluate to what extent control performance can be improved by applying theoretical methods in practical environments, and to explore how control performance can be further enhanced under real-world conditions.</description></item><item><title>Activities</title><link>https://trigger-fk.github.io/activities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://trigger-fk.github.io/activities/</guid><description>OUXT Polaris (2023.04 - Present) Software Developer: Perception Quadrotor Developer PR Manager Award RoboBoat 2025 Special Award (Persistence Exemplified) Domestic Conference 大西 凌平, 二見 堅太, 藤岡 怜生, 松崎 史弥, 西田 祐也,
RoboBoat2025 のための自律航行型無人船の開発,
ロボティクス・メカトロニクス講演会, 山形, 6月6日, 2025. 松崎 史弥, 岡本 健太, 吉本 幸太郎, 小林 聖人, 片岡 大哉, 永田 暁久, 西田 祐也,
Maritime RobotXへの挑戦を通じた技術活動,
第41回日本ロボット学会学術講演会, 宮城, 9月11日, 2023. Tech Conference: 藤岡 怜生, 二見 堅太, 糸園 朔, 松崎 史弥, 片岡 大哉, 小林 聖人,</description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>https://trigger-fk.github.io/publications/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://trigger-fk.github.io/publications/</guid><description>Jounal Article N. Gerdpratoom, F. Matsuzaki, Y. Yamamoto, and K. Yamamoto,
Enhanced Sampled-Data Model Predictive Control via Nonlinear Lifting,
Internatinal Journal of Robust and Nonlinear Control, Early View, 2025.
F. Matsuzaki and T. Ikeda,
Sparse Topology Estimation for Consensus Network Systems via Minimax Concave Penalty,
IEEE Control Systems Letters, vol. 8, pp. 1012&amp;ndash;1017, 2024.
International Conference F. Matsuzaki and T. Ikeda,
Sparse topology estimation for consensus network systems via minimax concave penalty,</description></item></channel></rss>